2052 - GREENLAND
SYSTEM FAILURE / VIRUS DETECTED
PROJECT HORIZON
ADVENTURE AT THE HEART OF DIGITAL
Technician: Okay, we're rolling, you can go.
Swann: Welcome to the Data Palace! Swann and Ismail here.
We are in charge of this data center, which was designed to store resource data important to scientists worldwide.
Ismail: So, if you're seeing this message, it's because we actually need your help.
Uh, there was a major cyberattack a few hours ago, and it has disrupted many of the data center's systems.
Swann: We are going to leave to fix the center's network manager systems,
but we need all the skills and intelligence of IT specialists like you to fix all the other systems.
Swann: By the way Hal, can you give us the list of problems?
HAL: According to the diagnostic system, several servers are close to overheating.
They must be cooled down urgently.
HAL: A blockage has been detected in ventilation duct 25B.
It must be removed as quickly as possible to reactivate the cooling systems.
Ismail: As you can see, there is a lot to do.
But don't hesitate to refer to the envelope you were given.
And if you need help, ask one of the technicians accompanying you.
Swann: You will need to work together to overcome the challenges that await you.
So don't hesitate to stick together.
Ismail: Thank you for your help and good luck to everyone!